blockbusterathome.com 2016-10-16

# 

DISH Websites Privacy Statement
Welcome to the DISH.com, mydish.com or dishanywhere.com website of DISH Network
L.L.C. and its subsidiaries (collectively, “DISH,” “we,” or “us”). This privacy statement
discloses the privacy practices for visitors to those websites and any other website
operated by DISH (collectively, the “websites”).
Children
DISH does not knowingly collect personally identifiable information from children under
the age of thirteen and does not wish to collect any such information.
Information Collection and Use
The information collected by DISH falls into two categories: (1) information voluntarily
supplied by you as a visitor to and/or user of the website and (2) tracking information
recorded as you navigate through the website. Some of this information is personally
identifiable information, but much of it is not. Personally identifiable information is
information that identifies you specifically; it does not include aggregate data or data that
does not identify you or other particular persons.
To make use of some features on our website, (for example, in order to process requests
for new services or make changes to existing products and services) you might need to
register and provide certain information as part of the registration process. We may ask
for your name, email address, street address, zip code, and credit card or financial
account information. We might also request information about your residence and number
of televisions. Supplying this information is entirely voluntary, but if you choose not to
supply the information, we may be unable to provide you with the products and services
we make available to other users of and visitors to our websites.
When you submit any personally identifiable information over the website, DISH (i) will
use the information for the purposes described at the time you submit it, and (ii) may use
the information to contact you to make you aware of other products and services of
interest. If you prefer to remain anonymous, you are still free to take advantage of the
publicly available content on our websites without registration.
In connection with the standard operation of DISH’s systems, certain non-personally
identifiable information about visitors to the websites is recorded. This information is used
primarily to tailor and enhance visitors’ experience using the website. We may use this
information in an aggregate, non-personally identifiable form to, among other things,
measure the use of our websites and determine which products and services are the most
popular with website visitors.
When an individual visits any Internet site, a unique address called an “IP address” is
recorded. DISH archives the log files in order to create aggregate statistical reports,
detect errors at the website, and for security reasons.
                                                 1

Reports for advertisement clicks are shared with the advertiser and advertising networks
as are cookies and calls. This information may be stored in DISH databases and/or those
of advertisers and advertising networks. However, advertisers usually have this
information already since their server captures it when a person clicks on an ad. This is
done to verify billing for the ads as well as for targeting and performance measurement.
DISH uses Google Analytics to collect information about traffic to this website. Google
Analytics is a web analysis service provided by Google. Google Analytics utilizes the data
collected to track and examine the use of websites, including ours, to prepare reports on
its activities and share them with other Google services. You can opt out of having your
information collected by Google Analytics by visiting here.
This website also uses the Google AdWords remarketing service to advertise on third
party websites to previous visitors to our sites. It could mean that we advertise to previous
visitors who have not completed a task on our site. This could be in the form of an
advertisement on the Google search results page, or a site in the Google Display Network.
Third-party vendors, including Google, use cookies to serve ads based on someone’s
past visits to other websites. Of course, any data collected will be used in accordance
with our own privacy policy and Google’s privacy policy. You can set preferences for how
Google advertises to you using the Google Ad Preferences page.
Disclosure of Personally Identifiable Information
We consider the personally identifiable information contained in our business records to
be confidential. We may sometimes disclose personally identifiable information about you
(including to our affiliates or to others who work for us) when it is necessary to conduct a
legitimate business activity related to the services we provide to you, and for other
reasons.
We also may be required by law or legal process to disclose certain personally identifiable
information about you to lawyers and parties in connection with litigation and to law
enforcement personnel. For example, we may be required by law to disclose personally
identifiable information about you without your consent and without notice in order to
comply with a valid legal process such as a subpoena, court order, or search warrant.
Cookies
Internet “cookies” may be used to customize our websites to the viewer. A cookie is a
standard feature of browser software. Cookies help us tailor and personalize our
websites. These cookies remain on your system and are automatically retrieved when
you visit at a later time. These cookies contain only information concerning the type of
customer (current or potential) and frequently visited pages. Typically, no other personal
information is stored in cookies.
Cookies may also be placed on your system by an Internet advertising network in order
to track the viewing of ads displayed on DISH websites. Because it is not required for you
to identify yourself, cookies cannot be associated with you if you elect not to log in or
identify yourself in any other way.
                                               2

Customers who are uncomfortable with the use of cookies have the option of disabling
them on their browser or may opt-out from dish.com tracking cookies here.
Notice to California Residents
DISH does not recognize “Do Not Track” requests from internet browsers.
Other websites
To make our website more valuable to our visitors, we may offer some features in
conjunction with other partners. Our website may also include links to other websites
whose privacy policies and practices may differ from ours. Once you leave our website,
the use of any information that you provide is governed by the privacy policy of the
operator of the website that you are visiting. We recommend that you read the privacy
policy of such other website.
Security
All information gathered on our websites is stored within a DISH database accessible only
to DISH and its specifically authorized contractors and vendors. However, we cannot
guarantee the complete security of our database, nor can we guarantee that information
you provide will not be intercepted while being transmitted to us over the Internet.
Changes to this Privacy Statement
We may change this notice at any time. If we do so, we will post the changes on our
website. By continuing to use the website after we post any changes, you accept and
agree to this privacy statement, as modified.
Privacy Policy for DISH Subscribers
This privacy statement discloses the privacy practices for certain DISH websites only. We
supply a copy of the privacy notice that applies to our satellite television subscribers
separately. You may view that privacy notice anytime by visiting
http://www.dish.com/service-agreements/ and clicking on the “Subscriber Privacy Notice”
link.
Version: January 2016
                                             3
